I've been in the palace for so long.
Tonight, I finally managed to sneak in here with Jingyuan's help.
Si Xingxuan.
You tyrant.
You slaughtered my entire clan
and killed my parents.
I won't let you live past tonight.
Rumor has it he's temperamental,
bloodthirsty, ruthless,
and kills without blinking an eye.
Capable of any evil.
Why does it seem to me
that he falls a bit short of that?
I am the best. Not bad.
Not bad.
Give you a CD from the past,
to listen to our love back then.
Sometimes it suddenly...
No, no.
If you keep singing,
I won't be able to control myself.
Your Majesty is amazing.
Exactly.
Right, right.
Oh my god.
What kind of world have I come to?
It seems
I need to get more familiar with this world.
Your Majesty, the meal is ready.
It will get cold if you don't eat now.
Your Majesty.
This is your favorite Hibiscus Ruby Tomato Soup.
I specially asked the imperial kitchen to prepare it for you.
When did I say I loved it?
Your Majesty, I...
Then tell me.
Which woman do I like?
And which place do I like to go to?
Your Majesty, I didn't mean it.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
So temperamental.
Do you think you can read my mind?
Why should Your Majesty be upset?
Just kill the disobedient ones.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Eunuch Sun isn't a good person either.
He tells the emperor to kill people at the drop of a hat.
Eunuch Sun, you really understand me.
You may all leave.
Leave at once.
No, I haven't taken my revenge yet.
I can't miss the opportunity tonight.
I am going to kill you.
Why are you not afraid of me?
Such a good opportunity.
It's a pity I don't have a knife.
I'm asking you.
Why are you not afraid of me?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is the Son of Heaven.
The Son of Heaven loves his people.
I am your people.
Why should I be afraid?
Interesting.
Since you are not afraid of me,
how about I promote you to a ninth-grade maid
to stay by my side?
He is definitely up to no good.
Your servant, Cangyue,
thanks Your Majesty.
Hey. Don't push.
Only three viewing spots are open a day.
Viewing time is limited.
This much. I was here first.
Mine, mine, mine, mine.
Hey, let's go.
Come earlier next time.
I am the best.
Your Majesty is amazing.
I love it.
Sold out.
What are you looking at?
His Majesty is practicing martial arts inside.
Practicing martial arts?
He is simply extraordinary.
So majestic.
Truly magnificent.
You like His Majesty?
Aren't you afraid of death?
What do you know?
When His Majesty is happy, he treats us very well.
So what if His Majesty kills people?
Who wants to be a maid forever?
Then how many can Your Majesty take on at once?
Five?
Fifty.
Fifty!
I can only take on four at a time.
Si Xingxuan alone can take on fifty.
Looks like I'll have to use my wits.